I'll call the other records scheduled to be in my office at Council for Monday April 17th, 2023. Public input on schedule personal chances we have none three consent agenda staff recommends will approve items four and five?
Okay, I walked through it tonight and that's like probably 60% complete maybe.
That is what i thought but
I just wanted to ask for a question.
Thank you, thank you.
Six bat six this bats services remember and of understanding with the auto county e911 trust authority
This is our annual contract on the number U at 9 one board it's them given us money currently give us 5000 month
and 1211 dollars a month to help us dispatch incentive longevity incentive
And that was pretty too disposed.
We're just renewing this amount of our MRE with 9 one board
It's the same as last year is it?
Yes, yeah nothing has changed we are potentially looking change in future once
Once again on your center if not 1 more do start feed for over this batch 4
And how about a bill and other so we may have others in the future right now where state says well
That's made down with a police on that building
I'm sorry, but there is no need to go
Right away from AT&T
To do something
We can't get some of those AT
We've been to the AT
We've been some really bad supply chain issues
Our project was the light almost a year it just came in last week
Generator is all here and half they couldn't get one
This has always very highly proprietary equipment
From this game of this thing's changed even for electrical
The equipment, you know
All of the systems are software, hardware all that stuff is now we're getting in
And even proprietary stuff and God love them
Everything it's just like
Even a new deal
We've got correct if were responded to the mistake
Our dispatch can actually put him on video
Tell what going onto us no while I'm running around
That's why
That's a lot of stuff
Absolutely
We're exciting stuff in this package and be wide saving
Great stuff, unfortunately it just putting a lot
Up his the pot together
It has been time consuming to get that done
I really feel like we are getting close
Put on a bit around
Stretch out about 100 times
Literally thought
Last summer last fall, last year
First day, I'm going go for a lot more
If I had to put it on
From a construction perspective, the standard answer is two weeks
Two week's has 2-weeks
So you know no more than just bought a rainy rain
Some scorned candy wine for everybody
Candy was dressed up and he puts my funds in that
We spend about 1.5 year ready
We have a lot of them with this product
I think car radios and water
And the water drive all other parts
It's just been a lot of moving parts and take one time in your life
Been down close wanting to know if he can vote on this
Or if you need lipstick stain
Okay, thank goodness for me
Second
Hi
Thank you
The discussion regarding the status is public works building fire
We'll see you in the next steps
Mr. Markew
He is 5 years older than he came from static light choice
We had vapor to build up this trans burn
Feel over into the bulk of time
Either a static set it off or
Hes said we have electrical sparks on layers
Had been in condoned wall with there's nothing
Vibrs when you watch video
It was big cloud
Explosions
One along the layer, air, air, air, air
He released two days later
Said we're done, you are good
We don't suspect anything
And then I'm going to send in regular driver of the gestures
They were flying into the house and he was George's and I
There would be a gesture coming in
A structural engineer coming
In tomorrows been taken through that point
The beams could have built
The heat was tremendous just giving idea
Fire wasn't in the northwest corner
Offs a catacorn, southeast quarters
Far structure about waste time
There wouldn’t no flame up there
It would have been this heat also
Everything that shot is devoured
To be able to do everything
We should track for an air
I'll find it
It was an excavator in there
The tabs on the metal to be surrounded
Tires didn't work
Tires were built and it ran away
Was that kind of heat higher you go
To eat its worst
That fire specter said he is probably a 1,300 degree city
Mark or have done an excellent job
We did not hold off fire
But we had tremendous heat there
Through the problem
We had to do some other stuff
All the bulbs got spot
Now there is start a rest
We are going in there
Everything has lost
And that's all five
That’s where we were at
When you go through all this process
It also like
To make it clear
Our city procurement guidelines
Give us an interview
To wave formal bid procedures for most purchases
And after review of these and review them with council
I do believe that this justifies
In the situation
Using emergency permit
Wouldn't be beneficial to city
Because it basically, if a jeopardizes public health
Safety economic loss
Or further damaged property of City money
It is in our best interest to move forward
We need the shop
To be up and running
And we have to maintain our equipment
We are planning on making our vehicles
Our machinery that
That will count every day
To keep city running
We’re going into taking place
First of all, what I am gonna take place
Who’s a new shopping
We’re going to use these procedures
To get this facility up and running
I think it is a good spot
Just on the way out
Which kept sound bay functional
Something more place
Or right now they can still function
Some one in south bay
So if we could start getting equipment
Some of the machinery and equipment
It tools in things replace
They can use them over there on south bay
While we’re rebuilding structure
On this way, it will be a bit more safe
I think it’s our best interest
We could basically responsible
while doing that quickly
So then you get up
Where is your funds?
I’ve got 5.3 million currently in our rainy day fund
We can use those funds
Until we start getting refunded from insurance
That was just a long-term day
And one of the next few days
If you came, fit it into that south bay
So it’s going to have be far and about
The labor bill will make 1517,000
Just lost at them
Before they were caught up with this cost
I think we got time to mess around guys
If the beams have been affected
It is safe for people being in a building hall
Nobody’s going into that section
The mechanics go there and try
To do an inventory
But as far or any work, looking at the freeing thing
They are not getting easily off limits
If it wins alone they don’t want them
Ina Billion Hall?
Yes
They are not on the building?
I don’t know, they don’t have a bank still
On inventory
There was double wall in there
We’ve got tar off at Norris Wall
The vertical beams support both side and for damage
But we’re going to wait until their here tomorrow
To expose those things
Because if you want anything that comes back
And say “You should do something”
I’ll talk about the legal counsel
What that means
And what i read in those guidelines is it allows me to reach out
To a number of you all, just fine
Have quick discussion and say here’s going
Here are the main things
There’re funding
It says “I have tipped at him”
So it’s not stopping from doing something
But certainly why not?
As far as how that’s happening
It doesn’t seem like we have to try this
It’s called a special meeting or anything
But all determined the appropriate steps in that
God willing what it means would be
And then I get a chance of talking about it
We’ve nowhere else, though
That’s how it’s going
To make sure you’re sitting on the right
There are some trucks and big issues
You can come from inside there with them
And once it was a heat issue you know, far
So let’s fire each of those trucks
It looks like our company is over still good
It’s just about time right there
Covering the wall and its order that never's going
But what I can tell i didn’t see work
You don’t have any thing to damage them, lower
Well luckily we’re talking around about red iron
Tanned
Not talkin'about employee they got hurt
That that’s all right
I’m getting in
I will definitely fill you all in
The more i learned about how we can do this
Alright number eight, ordinance 2023-03
The closing and says vacation
Thank you
To public use of the Public Way and Aliy Located
In a city my am situated on block 25
Result plat
And retaining right at any holder, the franchise
Determined by governing body to have
Relage granted by the ordinance or legislative
An actment maintain their existing utilities
In a emergency, has recommended about
The city is only planning to mission
There’s your whole presentation. You don’t even need top there
I know
So basically block 25
Reginald plat
It’s where nine tribes
And they’re reasonable high school set
I got marked down here with the Momma Hazard Authority
So, i was called basically
It is told that
The Aliy original in
Inthe Interatory plat from like 1896
There’s never vacated
So i went and looked at the replay of 1919
It has been vacated, it is high school all a lot
All that Aliy's being vacationed
When High School was built
I am not sure what year were built
That’s where we have our back to plat
It goes 1919
You’re good build, Uncle
We know in 1969
When it was the last high school class
They tore down build mine tribes
Apparently, apparently wasn’t caught in
So we’re getting max credit on this project they are doing
At my time towers nine tribes
Discovered that
It is never officially vacated
Here’s our underbureth later
Doing right and making an official
So that’s what this one is
Basically vacated the Aliy
Block when I drive sits
Marks your thing questions
Why does he catch it now?
You have a plat show, you got a plat
There are his ones in here
If look on to very last page
It’s for the...
Yeah
That's on page
Inthe Interatory
Page 6
Look that’s the original Indian territory plat
From 1987
I didn’t play them all
I’m not playing the whole plat
So they became a good tell
That’s from 1947
Then, The Replats
From 1919
Showing when High School
Clearly see that it is the Aliyas in the Hots are on plat
And again It wasn't caught
For 70s when Nontraps built
I guess it wasn’t the Skogi title
They are those ones that researched
For The Minimum Housing Authority
And there’s a one thats discovered
That is never vacated
So, if you check
I’m making most of them improve
Second
Five
Number 9 will be emergency cause for that same ordinance
Take a lot of time to prove
Number 5
So full of Williams
Alright
This is a occasion to write
The Martian ordinance 20
Do it
Oh, shut up, damn
It's kind too late now
But the Martians 2020
2012 A E Mending in rewriting chapter 4
Animals OfThe Code Abortances
Providing Surability
Providing for conflicting provisions
For building all conflicting ordinances
And establishing effective date
Most importantly, this incorporates the peace schedule
That you all prove it to theory
A couple weeks ago
As far as the substantive changes
Probably a major issue
And basically I think of some others
We’ve had some issues come up
Somebody has had possession of an animal for years
But they say, well I I’m not the owner
It’s my sister.
Just holding this thought on her sister
Well that is caused some problems
And it’s just clarifies
If you are really asking like never
Before a long period
At least between
That person in city
You Are The Elper
It doesn’t address the issue between
That person and whoever they’re saying
The real other is, but for purposes of our own
That’s just saying that They are
I don’t know if we’ll make it a couple
Other substantive changes
But i think there was one main thing
We’ve changed again
Because the type load has been confirmed
We have already seen changes
We’re kind of going through our whole thing
And we try to be best
To just redraft the entire order
Talking about only helps with personal and that
What That allows them
Is if it would have room for an actual owner
It will allow a person thats cared
For The Dog, or two years
Or whatever they are doing at this sort
If you don’t know how it’s done
If you start using this order in the 30
We have room for surrenders
So we can't be all opportunity to put that into effect
You guys Have a starting running your ticket yet
Because they don’t kind of get hooked
That will do an act as if it is going
I hear yu got its still getting called out alot
Make A Motion, and we improve
Hi
Alright, 11 is the emergency clause for that same ordinance
Motion
So go to the police
Aye
12 open-way litigation settlement
Through The Attorney General’s Office, Authorities City Manager Sign
We said division settlement participation
The lady got some shame in regards to the opioid litigation
That we agreed
To participate in a year ago
Although, he has not gotten here
But detail about this one
As We did with previous ones
I would point out that
We haven’t actually recently received many from the prior one
But the first litigation
Belt with The Attorney General's settlement
With some of its drug manufacturing
This one is by
Of these largest drugs distribution companies
They include Tiva, Outletune
CBS World Reams and Wallmark
Beyond that
We don’t have a lot more information
Other than the deadline
The Board Getting It Turned In is tomorrow
I m like A Motion, we give this any manager authorization
Second
Aye
13 other new business of Any which is a residence post in
This agenda
14 staff reports 15 Mayor Council Community and Naltzments
I want to say the community cleanups
We have been going on for probably a month or so
Maybe it will be longer in that
Of course, Berkeley has done several years
That is part of the time
Just having as parents
It started changing things
A little bit
In general with the show page
I started a little bit
Yesterday they did one from about 22nd
And went east to Mushroom Farm Road
and picked up 8,000 pounds of trash
Which was pretty amazing
That is really shocking
There's that much trash there
And I have helped with a few of them
When you start, that much trash here
But then when it is done
You see all the bags picked up
Gosh what else?
My grandpa would whip my tail
Throw stuff out like this
We had the young boys J. and Osborne
Jay was probably 7 or 8 years old
He did a trash pick-up
He picked up 4,5 bags of trash there
I like where it is going
Like the fact that people are getting involved
Getting down really helps
Makes things look a lot better
You don't realize how to drive by
Did make big difference
So probably put on our parcel, having less of them
Our next council meeting will be
The study station
And I would like to have it on there for us
To talk about
Leaders of the community, they need some of them
Our districts
The track is going behind us
That's lead at trying get stuff done
So we talked back next time around
He'd come out down if he liked or whatever
We'll just talk right now
Next time around
If you give a chance
Join in one piece
It's pretty rewarding actually
When you see it when your done
Number 16
City Manager Communications
Some members of the council I got a couple items on here
One dimension first this week
Starting Thursday and running through Saturday
We have The Mymlittle Theatre Production
Of 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling B
So that is my mlittle theatre production
7 to 9 p.m
And then Saturday
230-4 30
One of the things that's kind different from this particular production
The others is they will actually have four audience members
That would participate on stage in the spelling B as part
Of
Production
Of the spelling B
You should be there
See if you can get a response to it
I think that's what they would do
It was for me
But we're excited about
They always did fantastic job with their productions
And then of course, thats this week
Then also wanted mention again
The mural fest is coming up on 29th
We have a 10 year list of this month
And that's ten A.M to 3 p.m
On Saturday April 29th
we'll be having 10 muralist painting
With the art market, car show
Vintertans food trucks
I believe our chickenful egg
Food truck will either as well
So it should turn out
It certainly won everybody in the community
I'm your office
17 in German motion
Second
Okay
Thank you
Thanks man